Hello.
- What happened to Mrs. Black?
- My predecessor? She was paroled.
So you're the new
executive secretary, huh?
Don't let that title deceive you.
I do everything but wipe windshields.
- I'm Mitch Wayne.
- Yes, I recognized you.
- I'm Lucy Moore.
- Recognized me? From where?
Oh, come now. Surely you realize...
how often your photograph
has graced our tabloids?
But the captions
usually read, "Kyle Hadley,
Prince Charming of the oil empire,
and friend."
The dashing Kyle Hadley.
I saw him dash
through the office recently.
Seems he misplaced his money belt.
- Again?
- A hat was passed, and I contributed $16.47.
Well, for that, you ought to get
an oil well named after you.